#### PERSONAL DETAILS

Name: Carolyne Jebor Kimetto

Address: Flat 1, 586 North Circular Road, Dublin 1

**Telephone**: +353 879807398

Email: jeborcaro@gmail.com

Year of Birth: 1996

Language: English

### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

A passionate professional with experience in research, finance, administration, marketing, and community service. Having graduated with an Actuarial science degree and worked in different organizations, I have developed a strong administrative, and extensive technical background. I possess a strong desire to deliver world class service and make significant impact in any operations. I would be a very valuable asset to any organisation working closely with senior management in scaling, and delivering results.

#### **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS**

23<sup>rd</sup> Jan 2023 - To Date: TECHNOLOGICAL UNI. DUBLIN Masters Qualifier in Computing

3<sup>rd</sup> Sept 2014 - 14<sup>th</sup> Dec 2018: KISII UNIVERSITY. Bachelor of Actuarial Science

3<sup>rd</sup> Feb 2010 - 30<sup>th</sup> Nov 2013: BAHATI GIRLS SEC SCHOOL. Secondary Education

4th Jan 1998 - 28th Dec 2009: CRESCENT ACADEMY. Primary Education

### **PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS**

29th June 2017: KASNEB CIFA (Section 1)

### **SKILLS**

- Data analysis
- Customer service
- Proficient in Microsoft programs; Word, Excel, Publisher and Power point.
- Basic skills in R Software, Python Software and advanced Excel.
- Exceptional communication and presentation skills.
- Excellent analytical and problem solving skills.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### 1st JANUARY 2022 - 31st OCTOBER 2022

#### TECHNICAL ASSISTANT: NECOFA KENYA

- Generally responsible for technical production and ensuring success of the project.
- Involved in collection, drafting and submission of monthly reports of the project.
- Responsible for preparing site reports on expenditure and sales.
- Networked to link the company with the community.

### 1st JUNE 2021 - 31st DECEMBER 2021

#### ADMINISTRATIVE / RESEARCH ASSISTANT: RAE TRUST LIMITED

- Involved in the effective coordination and implementation of RAE administrative, office and research work.
- Compiling, formatting, and analysing RAE research work and field data.
- Involved in the preparation of grant materials and provision of timely data summary for granting agencies reports.
- Provision of research support and field research assignments.

## 9th MARCH 2020 - 31st MAY 2021

#### OFFICE ASSISTANT: RAE TRUST LIMITED

- Involved in the accurate recording, analysis, and computerization of RAE office work and field data.
- Planned and coordinated office work and field activities.
- Reported on the status of RAE services to the management.
- Put down minutes during meetings.

## 1st AUGUST 2019 - 29th FEBRUARY 2020

# INTERN: CORAT AFRICA

- Involved in marketing, planning and organizing training programs.
- Inputted all training materials and data into the supervisor's database.
- Scheduled appointments and assisted trainees with registration and finding the necessary information.
- Worked with the supervisor to compile reports on donor commitments.

### 1st MAY 2018 - 31st AUGUST 2018

### INTERN: NATIONAL SOCIAL SECURITY FUND

- Involved in administration, registration and collection of member contributions.
- Promoted NSSF growth program through field walks and trainings.
- Uploaded payroll data using NSSF E-service.

### **TRAININGS ATTENDED**

1<sup>st</sup> April 2019 - 5<sup>th</sup> April 2019: Customer service training by: Corporate Staffing Services

25<sup>th</sup> Oct 2017 – 24<sup>th</sup> Nov 2017: Data analysis course by: Dalworth Consult

14<sup>th</sup> June 2014 – 16<sup>th</sup> July 2014: Computer packages by: Benedita College

# **REFEREES**

a) Happiness Kerubo – Director (Necofa -Kenya)

**Mobile**: +254 727991302

Email: happineshem@gmail.com

b) Immaculate Pendo – Compliance Officer (NSSF Nyamira)

**Mobile**: +254 726996634

Email: immaculatependo@gmail.com

c) Otieno Calvins – Head of Operations (Bluewave Insurance)

**Mobile:** +254 717951507

Email: otienocalvins1@gmail.com